Hi, I'm Anthony, the product lead here at Udacity for robotics.
嗨 我是 Anthony 优达学城的机器人产品负责人
You've already learned a lot of syntax in C++,
你已经在 C++ 中学习了很多语法
including how to write functions and classes.
包括如何编写函数和类
Now you should feel confident that anything you could write in Python,
现在你应该自信满满 觉得自己可以用 Python 编写任何代码
you could also write in C++.
同时 也可以用 C++ 编写代码了
But let's take a step back and talk about why are you learning C++ in the first place.
不过 我们先不着急开始 首先谈谈为什么你要学习 C++
It basically comes down to the fact that certain C++ programs run faster.
根本原因是 某些 C++ 程序运行速度更快
Autonomous vehicles need to make
无人驾驶车需要快速做决定
quick decisions to successfully operate in a dynamic environment.
才能在动态环境中成功驾驶
Slicing off fractions of this millisecond from your programs might not seem like a lot,
从你的程序中的这个毫秒里节省一部分看起来并不多
and maybe it isn't for just one occurrence of an instruction.
这段时间 甚至不足以执行一条指令
But self-driving cars execute billions or
不过无人驾驶车能够在非常短的时间内
trillions of instructions in a small amount of time.
执行数十亿或者数万亿条指令
So those milliseconds add up very quickly.
所以这些时间会迅速累积
Efficient code is very important if you want your car performing
如果你想让汽车能在你期望的时候立即执行指令
an action when you're expected to and not seconds later.
而不是等待几秒 代码效率非常重要
But how do you get your programs to run faster when using C++?
但是 如何让你的程序在使用 C++ 时运行得更快呢？
Well, once you have a program that runs correctly,
一旦你有一个可正常运行的程序
you go through a process called code optimization.
你必须经历一个叫做代码优化的过程
Code optimization generally allows your program to use less memory,
代码优化通常可以让程序使用更少的内存
increase power efficiency, or execute faster.
提高电源效率 或者执行速度更快
For this lesson, we are going to primarily focus on getting C++ code to execute faster.
在本课中 我们主要关注如何让 C++ 代码更快地执行
For almost every line of code you write,
对于你写的每一行代码
the computer will execute a corresponding instruction like writing to or from memory,
计算机将执行相应的指令 如写入或读取内存
or running a mathematical calculation.
或者运行数学计算
Even something simple like assigning an integer to a variable
甚至像是将一个整数赋值给一个变量这样简单的指令
requires a computer to execute a set of instructions and write to memory.
也要求计算机执行一组指令并写入内存
Usually there are multiple ways to write a program and achieve the same results.
通常 有多种方式可以编写程序并达到相同的结果
And if you find a solution that requires fewer instructions for the computer to execute,
如果你找到了一个解决方案 可以让计算机执行更少的指令
well then quite simply your code will run faster.
那么很显然 你的代码将运行得更快
We have split this lesson into two parts.
我们把这一课分成两部分
First you will get an overview of what is happening inside
首先你会了解 当你编译和运行 C++ 程序时
the computer when you compile and run a C++ program.
计算机内部发生了哪些事情
This will give you some insight into what causes your program to slow down.
这会让你大致了解到程序变慢的原因
Then you will take what you've learned and use it to optimize C++ code.
然后 你将根据学到的知识来优化 C++ 代码
When you complete this section,
当你完成本部分学习时
you will walk away with the ability as you would say to empathize with the computer.
你会掌握如何以计算机的方式思考问题